const QuestionList = [
    {
      question:
        "Almatti Dam is on which of the following rivers?   ",
      answers: ["Krishna", "Kaveri", "Tungabhadra", "Malprabha"],
      correct: "Krishna",
      questionId: "1",
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which of the following states is India’s largest Bauxite producer"?',
      answers: ["Odisha", "Jharkhand", "Rajasthan", "Karnataka"],
      correct: "Jharkhand",
      questionId: "2",
    },
    {
      question:
        "With which of the following countries, India shares maximum length of border?",
      answers: ["Pakistan", "China", "Bangladesh", "Nepal"],
      correct: "Bangladesh",
      questionId: "3",
    },
    {
      question: "Amaravati, Arkavathy, Bhavani, Chinnar, Hemavati, Honnuhole, Kabini etc. Are tributaries of which among the following rivers?",
      answers: [
        "Kaveri",
        "Krishna",
        "Godavri",
        "Narmada",
      ],
      correct: "Kaveri",
      questionId: "4",
    },
    {
      question: "Amaravati, Arkavathy, Bhavani, Chinnar, Hemavati, Honnuhole, Kabini etc. Are tributaries of which among the following rivers?",
      answers: ["Sikkim", "Meghalaya", "Arunachal pradesh", "Manipur"],
      correct: "Arunachal pradesh",
      questionId: "5",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Indravati Hydro Electric Project belongs to which state?",
      answers: [
        "Tamil nadu",
        "Orissa",
        "Karnataka",
        "Andhra pradesh",
      ],
      correct: "Orrisa",
      questionId: "6",
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which among the following is the origin of Damodar river ?',
      answers: ["Greater Himalaya", "MKumaon Himalaya", "Shayadri Hills", "Chota Nagpur"],
      correct: "Chota Nagpur",
      questionId: "7",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The following hills are present where Eastern Ghats and Western Ghats meet ?   ",
      answers: ["Cardamom Hills", "Anamalai Hills", "TNilgiri hills", "Shayadri hills"],
      correct: "Nilgiri Hills",
      questionId: "8",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Bring out the only incorrect statement?",
      answers: [
        "Maximum Jute Mills in India are in West Bengal",
        "Maximum Jute Mills in India are in Cooperative Sector",
        "KMaximum Wool produced in India is of Carpet Grade",
        "Maximum woolen units in decentralized sector in India are in Punjab",
      ],
      correct: "Maximum Jute Mills in India are in Cooperative Sector",
      questionId: "9",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Mullaperiyar Dam” has been a long pending issue between which of the following two states?   ",
      answers: ["Karnataka & Kerala", "KAndhra Pradesh and Tamil Nadu", "Karnataka & Tamil Nadu", "Tamil Nadu and Kerala"],
      correct: "Tamil Nadu and Kerala",
      questionId: "10",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the approximate length of the Brahmaputra Plain?   ",
      answers: ["500 km", "720 km", "T1130 km", "1450 km"],
      correct: "720 km",
      questionId: "11",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is the highest peak of the Himalayan range in India?   ",
      answers: ["K2", "Kanchenjunga", "Nanda Devi", "Mt.Everest"],
      correct: "Kanchenjunga",
      questionId: "12",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Nathu La Pass is situated in which of the following range?   ",
      answers: ["Vindhyas", "Karakoram", "Western Ghat", "Himalayas"],
      correct: "Western Ghat",
      questionId: "13",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Ananthagiri Hills is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
      answers: ["Madhya Pradesh", "Telangana", "Chattisgarh", "West Bengal"],
      correct: "Telangana",
      questionId: "14",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Mount Abu is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
      answers: ["Rajasthan", "Madhya Pradesh", "Uttar Pradesh", "Karnataka"],
      correct: "Rajasthan",
      questionId: "15",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is the new name of the Ross island?   ",
      answers: ["Mahatma Gandhi Island", "Abdul Kalam Island", "Jawaharlal Nehru Island", "Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose Island"],
      correct: "Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose Island",
      questionId: "16",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is the longest Drive-In Beach in Asia?   ",
      answers: ["Muzhappilangad Beach", "Kollam Beach", "Marari beach", "Fort Kochi beach"],
      correct: "Muzhappilangad Beach",
      questionId: "17",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Katchh & Kathiawar Peninsula are separated from each other by which of the following gulfs/ Bays?   ",
      answers: ["Gulf of Katchh", "Gulf of Khambat", "Gulf of Mannar", "Gulf of Aden"],
      correct: "Gulf of Katchh",
      questionId: "18",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The Bhander Plateau is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
      answers: ["Madhya Pradesh", "Jharkhand", "Maharashtra", "Karnataka"],
      correct: "Madhya Pradesh",
      questionId: "19",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is the northern most island of Nicobar island?   ",
      answers: ["Little Nicobar", "Car Nicobar", "Great Nicobar", "Teressa island"],
      correct: "Car Nicobar",
      questionId: "20",
    },
    {
      question:
      "Damodar through divided ranchi plateau in the north from which of the following plateau?",
      answers: ["Koderma Plateau", "Hazaribagh Plateau", "Singhbhum Plateau", "None of the above"],
      correct: "Hazaribagh Plateau",
      questionId: "21",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The Meghalaya Plateau is detached from the Indian peninsula by which of the following?   ",
      answers: ["Great Boundary Fault", "Himalayan Frontal Fault", "Goranghat gap", "Malda Gap"],
      correct: "Malda Gap",
      questionId: "22",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The southern part of the Karnataka plateau is known as by which of the following name?   ",
      answers: ["Barkhan", "Malnad", "Maidan", " Hamada"],
      correct: "Maidan",
      questionId: "23",
    },
  
    {
      question:
        "Sigur Plateau is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
      answers: ["Karnataka", "Kerala", "Andhra Pradesh", "Tamil Nadu"],
      correct: "Tamil Nadu",
      questionId: "24",
    },
    {
      question:
      " Zuari river is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
      answers: ["Goa", " Maharashtra", " Kerala", "Arunachal Pradesh"],
      correct: "Goa",
      questionId: "25",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Almatti Dam is on which of the following rivers?   ",
      answers: ["Krishna", "Kaveri", "Tungabhadra", "Malprabha"],
      correct: "Krishna",
      questionId: "1",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Almatti Dam is on which of the following rivers?   ",
      answers: ["Krishna", "Kaveri", "Tungabhadra", "Malprabha"],
      correct: "Krishna",
      questionId: "1",
    },
  ]
  
  var QuestionBank = (n = 1) =>
    Promise.resolve(QuestionList.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n))
  
  export default QuestionBank
  